>> Brian Holt: 因此 Reach 路由器有两个主要的路由器。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So Reach Router, there's
there's two major routers for React.
其实现在可能还有另外一个叫纳维的
And actually now there's probably three
there's another one called NaVi that just
我真的不太懂
came out that I don't
really know too much about.
我只知道它是站起来的，人们喜欢它。
I just know that it's up and
coming and people like it.
但历史上都有 React 路由器和 Reach 路由器
But historically there's been
React router and Reach router,
Ryan Florence 是由类似的人撰写的
which are authored by similar people,
Ryan Florence wrote.
同时， React 路由器也可以使用 React 路由器。
Reach router and
he also helps with React router as well.
所以我们今天要用 Reach 路由器
So we're gonna use Reach router today.
我是 Reach 路由器的粉丝，因为它的功能非常集中，对吧 ?
I'm a big fan of Reach router because
it's very accessibility focused, right?
所以如果你有一个页面改变它会聚焦在右边的页面上
So if you have like a page change
it'll focus on the right page,
而关注焦点是一个非常困难的事情。
and managing focus is
a really difficult thing.
如果你不知道这就意味着你需要
And if you don't know that it's
a difficult thing that means you need to
在辅助功能选项方面更加努力，因为这很困难，而且
work harder on accessibility probably,
because it is difficult and
那也是值得的，你应该做的事情。
it's also worthwhile,
something you should be doing.
所以， React 路由器，不是在辅助功能上不好，不是，但是
So React router, it's not that it's
bad at accessibility, it's not, but
它只会让你处理很多无障碍的事情
it just makes you handle a lot
of accessibility things.
Reach 路由器会为你处理很多问题他们很聪明
Reach router handles much of that for
you and they're smart about it, so
这是个很好的计划
it's a good project to look at.
> > Brian Holt:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And that being said,
他们的工作相当相似他们都是伟大的项目
they work relatively similar
they're both great projects.
如果您对学习 React 路由器版本三感兴趣
If you're very interested in
learning React router version three
在此过程中，请使用此 React 路由器。
of this course, use this React router.
它仍然完全有效，它们仍在同一主版本上。
It's still totally valid,
they're still on the same major version.
那就去吧
So yeah, go ahead and
如果想了解 React 路由器，请检出版本 3 。
check out version three if you
wanna learn about React router.
>> Brian Holt: 现在，我们想做的是，我们想添加第二个页面，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now, what we wanna
do is, we wanna add a second page,
详细信息页面，对吧 ?
a details page, right?
所以我们要有个单页申请
So we're gonna have
a single page application.
现在只需要谈谈关于单页应用的问题
Now, just a second to talk
about single page applications,
并非每个应用程序都需要是单个页面应用程序。
not every app needs to be
a single page application.
有多个不同的页面来加载不同的东西是可以的，对吧 ?
It's okay to have multiple different
pages that load different things, right?
所以我要展示如何做到这一点，所以这是你工具箱里的另一个工具。
So I'm just gonna show how to do this,
so this is another tool in your toolbox.
但是不要觉得你总是要有一个单一的页面应用，对吧 ?
But don't feel like you always have to
have a single page application, right?
我想一个很好的例子是Fron趋向大师的网站，对吧 ?
I think a good example of that is
the Frontend Masters website, right?
这不是单页应用程序，它们做得非常好。
It's not a single page application and
they did it really well.
>> Brian Holt: 但类似 Netflix 的内容是单页应用程序和
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But something like
Netflix is a single page application and
有道理吧
that makes sense, right?
这是一种非常应用的感觉
It's a very app like feel.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，我要你做的就是我希望你回到你的代码
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so what I want you to
do is I want you to go back to your code
我希望您创建一个新文件并调用此 details.js。
editor here and I want you to create
a new file and call this details.js.
>> Brian Holt: 好，而不是 details.js ，我们会说从反应中反应。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, instead of details.js
we're gonna say import React from react.
你可能已经厌烦了
You're probably sick of writing that now.
>> Brian Holt: 您会说 const 详细信息等于箭头函数，对于
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And you'll say const
Details equals arrows function, and for
现在我们只会把一些愚蠢的东西送回去
now we're just gonna
return something dumb.
>> Brian Holt: 就像那样。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Just something like that.
然后我们会说出口违约细节
And then we'll say export default Details.
布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 很明显我们稍后会解决这个问题
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Well,
obviously we're gonna fix this later,
这不是最后的结果不过是吧
this is not what this is gonna
end up looking like, but yeah.
>> Brian Holt: 现在，我们需要安装 Reach 路由器。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now, at this point
we need to go install Reach router.
我只想让包裹为我做
I'm just gonna let parcel do it for me,
cutz 我在命令行里有个包裹在这里
cuz I have parcel running right
here in the command line.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，在上面的 app.js中，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
at the top here in app.js,
我要用卷发来输入类似的路由器
I'm gonna say import Router
like that with curly
从 @reach/router ( 如 @reach/router ) 周围的花括号括起。
braces around it from @reach/router,
like that.
再次记住，如果我这样做，你可以在这里看它。
And again remember, that parcel if I do
this and you can watch it down here let's
为我安装该装置 >> Brian Holt: 但是
install that for me
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But
如果不是您，那么必须执行 npm 安装到达路由器。
if not you then you have to go
do npm install reach router.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，看起来是重建。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
looks like it's rebuilding.
所以现在我想做的不是一直在渲染搜索媒体
So now, I wanna do instead of just always
rendering search press which is what we're
现在正在做对吧
doing right now, right?
我希望在搜索页面或搜索页面之间切换
I want to switch between rendering
either the search page or
详细信息页面，对吗 ?
the details page, right?
我要做的就是把路由器放了
So what I'm gonna do here
is I'm gonna put router.
>> Brian Holt: 然后，我将在路由器内部放置 SearchParams 。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then oops, I'm gonna
put SearchParams inside of the router.
> > Brian Holt: 然后在下面我要详细说明细节。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then underneath
that I'm gonna put Details.
现在注意我还没有输入详细信息
Now, notice I haven't I haven't
imported details as well but
用 Visual Studio 代码来形容
with Visual Studio code it says hey,
您正在尝试使用详细信息组件，并且您有一个称为详细信息的文件。
you're trying to use the details component
and you have a file called details.
我很确定你在这里也要用同样的东西
I'm pretty sure you're trying
to use the same thing here.
所以我就点击这个你就会注意到
So I'll just click this, and
you'll notice up here that
对我来说是很重要的事对吧
are important details up here for
me, which is convenient right?
但是，我又要在这里做 5 行，从细节中输入细节。
But again I have to do this line 5 there,
import details from details like that.
>> Brian Holt: 然后你必须给他们路径，所以
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
then you have to give them paths, so
我要说的是 " path= / details/:id " 。
I'm gonna say path=
/details/:id like that.
我还得给 SearchParams 提供路径，我指的是 /。
And I have to give SearchParams
the path as well, I mean the path of /.
>> Brian Holt: 这是 React 路由器不同于 Reach 路由器的另一种方法。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So this is another way that
React router differs from Reach router.
React 路由器将呈现匹配的所有内容，而 Reach 路由器仅为
React router will render everything that
matches, whereas Reach router is only
才能把最匹配的东西
going to render the the thing
that matches the most.
我想说的是一个很主观的事情
Which is I realize a very
subjective thing to say,
因为你能有两种技术在技术上是一致的
because you can have two things that
technically match the same thing.
就像这样如果我说你不用跟着我
Like this, if I said,
you don't have to follow with me here,
我给你举个例子还有其他路线
I'm just gonna give you an example,
some other route.
我说了路径 = /details/1。
And I said path = /details/1.
>> Brian Holt: 让我们在这里谈第二个话题。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Let's talk about
ID here for just a second.
这是变量对吧
This is a variable, right?
这是用路径做变量的很常见的方法，对吧 ?
This is a very common way of doing
variables with paths, right?
所以如果我放进去，请忽略 14 秒。
So if I put in,
just ignore a 14 for a second.
如果我放进去我把它放进我的 URL里
If I put in this, and
I put in /details/15 into my URL,
它会把那个 ID 传给那个组件吧
it's gonna pass that ID
into that component, right?
这样就能匹配了对吧
So it'll match this, right?
有道理吗
Does that make sense?
好吧如果我有这两条路
Okay, now,
if I have these two routes here,
哪条路线更具体?
which of these routes is more specific?
>> Brian Holt: 显然还有其他路线，如人类一样，我们会看到
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Obviously some other route,
like as a human, we look at that and
对我们来说是很直观的对吧
that's very intuitive to us, right?
但他们其实就像一个计分算法
But they've actually put like a scoring
algorithm behind this that it'll choose
对你来说是最具体的路线对吧
the most specific route for
you, and it's good, right?
所以如果我放进 /ddetail/1， React 路由器也会呈现这两种情况，对吧 ?
So if I put in /detail/1, React router
would render both of these, right?
而 Reach 路由器只会呈现其他路线
And Reach router will just
render some other route,
我认为这是我们预期的直觉行为，对吧 ?
which I think is the intuitive
behavior that we would expect, right?
但这就是这样工作的方式。
But that's how that works.
有道理吗
Make sense?
好的
Okay, cool.
>> 扬声器 2: 此处声明的顺序是否重要?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So
does the order of declaration here matter?
>> Brian Holt: 没有。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: It does not.
>> 演讲者 2: 好的。 >> Brian Holt: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay.
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yeah.
问得好，不是。
Good question, it does not.
因此，在 React 路由器中，它们使用名为 Switch的东西。
So with React router they
use a thing called Switch.
如果你想做一个特别的路线
If you wanna do just one
particular route in that one,
第一次比赛就行了吧
it will do the first one it matches,
right?
所以在这个问题上它确实很重要但它是一个计分系统
So in that one it does matter, but
this one it does a scoring system and
然后在结束时取最高分 > Brian Holt: 也许我
then it picks the highest score at the end
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Maybe I
应该会少一点看多
should probably be a little
bit less bullish on that.
可能在某种程度上它可能会在评分算法中添加一点
It might matter at some point it might add
like one point in their scoring algorithm,
但在理论上我不认为这不重要
but in theory,
I don't think it shouldn't matter.
这就是他们对名誉的要求之一。
That was one of their claims to
fame was scoring system in it.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，现在我们有路由器了。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, cool so
now we have a router.
还有一些值得一提的关于 Reach 路由器的事
Something else that's worth mentioning
about Reach router is you can have
页面上的多个路由器。
multiple routers on the page.
所以你可以想象我有一个主页，我用一个路由器来做这个。
So you can probably imagine I have like
a main page and I use a router for that.
但我现在也可以有一个情境的网站，对吧 ?
But I could also have
a contextual site now, right?
这就像根据哪个页面修改侧边导航更改一样。
That like depending on which page
amend the side nav changes as well.
你还可以有一个路由器在那里有不同的规则
And you can also have a router over
there that has different rules and
不同的匹配模式。
different matching patterns.
这些也可以相互独立工作。
And those can work independently
of each other as well.
所以它非常灵活，它是一个非常强大的技术。
So it's quite flexible, it's a really
powerful piece of technology.
我们只是擦伤表面
And we are just gonna scratch the surface,
我不认为这会比这更重要对吧
I don't think it's gonna do very
much more than this, right?
我们会用这个和链接从 Reach 路由器里
We're gonna use this and links and
that's about it from Reach router.
所以你知道吗这不是关于 Reach 路由器的课程
So just so you know,
this is not a course on Reach router,
我只是选择一个给你看
I'm just choosing one to show you.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，现在我有了这个，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so,
now that I have that,
我们再看一下我们的网页
let's go take a look at our page, again.
>> Brian Holt: 所以我有这个，注意，在斜杠上，主页，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So I have this,
notice that on the slash, the home page,
它会到 params 页面上但如果我去 /details/1
it's going to the params page,
but if I go to /details/1.
看看上面写着什么，你好，对吧 ?
Look what it says, hi lol, right?
这就是我们预期的工作方式。
So this is working the way that we expect.
我们可以后退和前进
We can go backwards and forwards.